

CONTACT

Porto, Portugal

(+351) 963 402 337

luis.alves.sa@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/lsa003

EDUCATION

■ Business Intelligence and Analytics

2018 – 2019: Post graduation at Porto Business School

MsC in Engineering

2008: Electrical & Computers Engineering – Telecom at Faculdade de Engenharia da Universidade do Porto

☐ HSK I (Chinese 1st Level)

2014: Instituto Confúcio – Universidade de Lisboa

Tech Workshops

2010-2017 at Altran:

- Team Management & Communication Skills;
- Leadership & Time Management;
- Project Management & Financial Risk.

German A1

2008: German CEFR A1 at Lancaster College

EXPERTISE



LUÍS SÁ

DATA SCIENTIST / ENGINEER

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Over 10-years experience as an Engineer and Consultant, performing various roles, from technical expert to team leading/manager.

This experience allowed me to have a greater flexibility in the roles performed, improve my interpersonal relationship skills, namely in communication, team management and leadership, customer management and as well as conflict and time management.

PROFESSIONAL HISTORY

DATA SCIENTIST/ANALYST STUDENT • 2018 - TODAY

Business Intelligence & Analytics post-graduation at Porto Business School.

RAN CONSULTANT • JAN - MAY 2018

2G/3G Data Analysis & Report Presentation for Bouygues Telecom Architecture and Dimensioning team.

TEAM LEADER • 2014 - 2016

Ensure team management & best performance to achieve the desired quality of service delivered to customer.

SUPPORT & MAINTENANCE CONSULTANT • 2010 - 2017

Alcatel 2G Network Equipment Support & Maintenance Engineer (Hardware and Software troubleshooting).

1 **IP TRAINER •** 2010

IP and ATM Training performed in Luanda, Angola, to UNITEL Engineers.

ENGINEER / TEAM LEADER • 2008 - 2010

2G/3G Indoor coverage projects for Altice (former Portugal Telecom) and Vodafone.

For more detail please visit my website @ github or my linkedin profile.